A Guide to the Gordon and Webster Family Papers
University of Virginia Library
- Series IV: Webster Family: Richard Henry and Ann Gordon Webster
  - 1961 Webster general correspondence, 43 items (Box-folder 34:8)
    Correspondents include Peter S. Mansfield, Eileen Fletcher, Nancy Laub, Mary Bucknall, James Page Elder, Jane C. Johnson, Gladys Briggs, Vivian Owen, Mary and John Lincoln, Sylvia Holden, Clive Robinson, Jans Johnson who mentioned his low opinion of Dr. Hasting Kamuzu Banda, Donald J. Sterling, Gordon M. Morrison (Mac), Sallie Close, Abbot Fletcher, Mike Holmes, Marion Wheeler, Mary Stackpole, Alida Davison, Clara and Art Rall, and Anna Williams.
  - 1961 Webster general correspondence-Christmas Cards, 70 items (Box-folder 35:1)
    Correspondents include Donald J. Sterling, Martin Ochs, Alice Morrison, Martin and Paddy McLaughlin, Cynthia and Philip Laundry, Peggy Macleod, John Caswell, Mary and Steve Stackpole, Bayne and Harry Carey, Grace Fletcher, Atkins Family, John and Sandy Bastek, Jean and Ron Pewter. Bob and Vivian Owen, Reid B. Morrison ("Zipper"), Anne and Pat Hale, John and Gloria Gibson, Eileen Fletcher, Jennifer Davidson, Dorothy Balz, Ted and Claire Curtis, Ruth Chinamano, Bud and Patty Foulke, Damaris Hayman, Norman and Jean Reddaway, Hans and Adelaide Welser, and a generic card with photograph from Mr. and Mrs G. Mennen Williams.
  - 1962 Webster general correspondence, 26 items (Box-folder 35:2)
    Correspondents include Helen Robbins, Marty Swan, Jeannette Atkins, Clint Green and a news clipping on Soviet Spy Training, Mrs. John Emmerson, John P. Nugent, Mary Novotny, Ann Driver, Brenda Morris, Jane Willems, and Ashton B. Collins.
  - 1963-1965 Webster general correspondence, 36 items (Box-folder 35:3)
    Lewis J. Williams, Brenda Morris, Edward M. Korry ,(about his appointment as Ambassador to Ethiopa) Senator Vance Hartke, Barny Howard, (and his article on Free Speech) B. P. Whipple, Rufus Smith, Anna Williams, John P. Nugent, Charlie Rushing, Clive Robinson, Paul and Dorothy Barringer, Richard A. Fuller, Hilde Schnitzer, John Harper, and Reid B. Morrison. Included is a letter from Ann Webster to Edward and Pat Korr, and a letter from Ann Webster to William M. Spackman at the University of Colorado about an article on poetry. There is also a telegram notifying the Webster's that James Southall Wilson had died.
  - 1966 Webster general correspondence, 19 items (Box-folder 35:4)
    Correspondents include Mary Coon, Betty Mustard, Reid B. Morrison, ("Zipper") Lou DeAngelis, Robert Allyn, John Snelling, Abbot and Eileen Fletcher, and Mrs. Alan Davidson.
  - 1967 Webster general correspondence, 19 items (Box-folder 35:5)
    Correspondents include Pat Rice, Caroline Conant, Gordon D. Davis, Lou DeAngelis, Eileen Fletcher, Donald J. Sterling, Dr. L. Herbert Loeb, and June Whelan.
  - 1968-1975n. d. (Maggie) Webster general correspondence, 15 items (Box-folder 35:6)
    Letters between Maggie and her school friends
  - 1968-1969 Webster general correspondence, 29 items (Box-folder 35:7)
    Correspondents include Frederick Brokaw, Alan Davidson, Evelyn [Wyllie] C. Taber, Caroline Conant, Mrs. Bruce Meeker, Dorothy Stevens, Kay Moore, Maxwell Fletcher, Herbert W. Warden, Joan Veitch, and J. M. Smith. There are also letters from Ann and Harry Webster to June Whelan.
  - 1970 Webster general correspondence, 18 items (Box-folder 35:8)
    Correspondents include Winfield Bennett, Robert S. Allyn, Cleveland C. Cram (who wrote about the death of CIA employee Paul Birdsall), and Caroline Conant. There are also letters from Ann Webster to Pam Ramsay, Caroline Conant, and others.
  - 1971-1972 Webster general correspondence, 28 items (Box-folder 35:9)
    Correspondents include Robert S. Allyn, Caroline Conant, Billie Mansfield, Andrew Onderdonk, Reid B. Morrison ("Zipper") and Thomas J. Barrett. There is also a letter from Ann Webster to Caroline Conant.
  - 1973-1975 Webster general correspondence, 14 items (Box-folder 36:1)
    Correspondents include Aristides George Lazarus, Peter Hesse, Helen Elder, and Caroline Conant.
  - 1976 Webster general correspondence, 13 items (Box-folder 36:2)
    Correspondents include Ruth Green, Aristides George Lazarus, Jeanne Delaney, Caleb L. Batten, Robert S. Allyn, and Caroline Conant.
  - 1977-1978 Webster general correspondence, 30 items (Box-folder 36:3)
    Correspondents include Caroline Conant, Abbot Fletcher, Jonathan Kebbe, Margaret Hench Underwood, Bernard Zilberg, Jane Bradley, and Charlie and Alida Davison. There are letters from Harry to Andrew Onderdonk.
  - 1979-1980 Webster general correspondence, 6 items (Box-folder 36:4)
    Correspondents include Caroline Conant, Phil Cherry. There are also letters from Harry to Andrew Onderdonk.
  - 1981-1982 Webster general correspondence, 19 items (Box-folder 36:5)
    Correspondents include Caroline Conant, Pam Ramsay, Vivian and Robert Allyn, Malcolm Aste, Mary Louise Merritt ("Weezie") and Audrey Highberger. There are also letters from the Webster family to Caroline Conant and Andrew Onderdonk.
  - 1983-1984 Webster general correspondence, 18 items (Box-folder 36:6)
    Correspondence includes Margaret Hench Underwood, Donald J. Sterling, Mary and Bill Wright, and Vivian Allyn. There are also letters from Harry to Andrew Onderdonk.
  - 1985-1986 Webster general correspondence, 20 items (Box-folder 36:7)
    Correspondents include Judy Fletcher, Andrew Onderdonk, Margaret Hench Underwood, and Vivian Allyn. There are also letters from Harry to Andrew Onderdonk.
  - 1987-1989 Webster general correspondence, 26 items (Box-folder 36:8)
    Correspondents include Vivian Allyn, Caroline Conant, Andrew Onderdonk, and Harry Webster.
  - 1990-1993 Webster general correspondence, 25 items (Box-folder 36:9)
    There are letters from Vesta Lee Gordon (The Book Broker) asking Ann Webster to contribute to the Stonefield Memorial. Other correspondents include Ann Wolff, Hoffman Wolff, Joseph Y. Rowe, Jonathan [Krebb], Dottie Conant, Ronald Ratcliff, Suzanne Simms, Gordon Cameron, and Paris Manfredonia. There are also letters from Harry Webster to Andrew Onderdonk, and Ann Webster to Pat Rice. Also included is a letter from Maggie Webster to Nancy Webster Barnes.
  - 1995 Webster general correspondence, 28 items (Box-folder 36:10)
    Correspondents include Vicky and Peter Cram, Caroline Davidson, Barbara Cherry, Pat Rice, Ann K. Warren, Mike and Audrey Highberger, Edith and Hans Wyss, Jane Hawxhurst, Sallie Starker, and Donald J. Sterling, Harry wrote about the Ann Gordon Webster Fellowship at George Washington University. Ann Gordon Webster died in 1994.
  - 1996-2001 Webster general correspondence, 15 items (Box-folder 37:1)
    There are many letters from Harry Webster to Pat Rice who was a good friend of Ann's and an intimate friend of Harry's after Ann's death. There are also letters from Webster family members to Pat Rice. Included are photographs from Douglas and Judy Woodbury.
  - n. d. Webster general correspondence, 37 items (Box-folder 37:2)
    Correspondence includes Andrew Onderdonk, Caroline Conant, Wyn Graham, Vivian Allyn, Wolfgang Arnicke, Donald Hopson, Alphonso Rodriquez, and Jean Holden.
  - n. d. Webster general correspondence, 29 items (Box-folder 37:3)
    Correspondents include Caroline Conant, Abbot Fletcher and others.
  - 1955-1969 V.I.P. Correspondence, 16 items (Box-folder 37:4)
    There is also correspondence concerning job opportunities for Harry from Roger W. Jones, Executive Office of the President; William P. Gormbley, Vice President of the Ford Foundation; William T. Golden; B. C. Christensen, IBM; Robert Ellsworth; William W. Scranton; Minos A. Zombanakis; Geoffrey Bell; Robert S. Allyn; and Grenville R. Holden, President of the Hyuck Corporation.
  - 19541961-1962 Christmas/Greeting Cards and gift lists, 5 items (Box-folder 37:5)
  - n. d. Christmas/Greeting Cards, 67 items (Box-folder 37:6)
  - n. d. Christmas/Greeting Cards, 64 items (Box-folder 37:7)
  - n. d. Christmas/Greeting Cards, 42 items (Box-folder 37:8)
  - n. d. Christmas/Greeting Cards and gift lists, 45 items (Box-folder 37:9)
  - 1946 Certificates for R. H. Webster, 15 items (Box-folder 38:1)
    Included is an honorable discharge certificate from the United States Army.
  - 1952-1954 Financial papers of R. H. Webster, 30 items (Box-folder 38:2)
  - 19511964-1969 Financial papers of R. H. Webster: household, 90 items (Box-folder 38:3)
    There are documents and correspondence relating to salary, insurance, automobiles, rent and other financial issues.
  - 1965-1969 Financial papers of R. H. Webster: stocks, 30 items (Box-folder 38:4)
  - 1954-1957 Financial papers of R. H. Webster: tax returns, 7 items (Box-folder 38:5)
  - 1964- Financial papers of R. H. Webster: travel receipts, 30 items (Box-folder 38:6)
    Included are various tickets for passages, travel vouchers, travel authorizations and reimbursement forms.
  - 1953-19541965 Foreign service papers of R. H. Webster, 8 items (Box-folder 38:7)
    There are lists of names and addresses for Government personnel in Madrid, Spain. There are also papers related to travel and work in Santo Domingo as well as a map of Santo Domingo with markings on it.
  - 195319671991 Health and medical records, 8 items (Box-folder 38:8)
    There is a signed document by Ann Webster describing the chain of events during the miscarriage of her second child. There are also doctor reports for her general health and for a gall bladder procedure in 1991.
  - 1957-1958 Household affairs: daycare, 67 items (Box-folder 38:9)
    There is correspondence about day care with various applicants and agencies.
  - 1949-19691992 Household affairs, 23 items (Box-folder 38:10)
    There is correspondence related to bills, dues and maintaining the house. There is a letter from Harry A. George of Keller and George, Jewelers and letters requesting information on preparatory schools for the children.
  - 1951-1955 Identification records, 2 items (Box-folder 38:11)
    There are passports for Ann and Harry Webster. There is also a birth certificate for Liza (Elizabeth Archer Webster) and "Oppit" (William Webster III).
  - 1961-1962 Invitations, 97 items (Box-folder 39:1)
    These are mostly social invitations related to Harry's work.
  - 194919641967n. d. Invitations, 46 items (Box-folder 39:2)
    Included is an invitation to the wedding of Ann Gordon and Harry Webster. There is also an invitation to the Queen of England's birthday party.
  - n. d. Wedding invitations, 3 items (Box-folder 39:3)
    Included are wedding invitations for the weddings of William Webster III and also for Elizabeth Archer Webster (Liza).
  - 1956-19571968n. d. Miscellaneous news clippings, 20 items (Box-folder 39:4)
    There are news clippings about the death of the last Civil War Union Veteran; the sinking of the ship, The Andrea Doria; death of a "Salon Hostess" from prohibition; death of Humphrey Bogart, and other items of interest.
  - 1966n. d. Miscellaneous news clippings, 6 items (Box-folder 39:5)
    There are news clippings about the CIA.
  - 1933n. d. Resume and reference letter for R. H. Webster, 4 items (Box-folder 39:6)
  - 1947-1948 Rhodes Scholarship, 12 items (Box-folder 39:7)
  - 1967-1968 Schools: American School in the Netherlands, 6 items (Box-folder 39:8)
  - 1967-1968 Schools: Groton, 3 items (Box-folder 39:9)
  - 1966-1967 Schools: Herbert Hoover, 1 item (Box-folder 39:10)
    Report card for Elizabeth A. Webster (Liza)
  - 1977 Schools: Madeira, 1 item (Box-folder 39:11)
    News letter for reunions photographs
  - 1971 Schools: Moses Brown, 1 item (Box-folder 39:12)
    Letter about the Alumni Association
  - 1947 Schools: Princeton, 7 items (Box-folder 39:13)
    Included is information about reunions and some classwork by Harry Webster.
  - n. d. Schoolwork, 19 items (Box-folder 39:14)
    School work and activities of Maggie Webster including a grade report from Tulane.
  - n. d. Photographs of Ann Gordon and Harry Webster, 12 items (Box-folder 39:15)
  - 1945 Photographs of Harry Webster in the service, 40 items (Box-folder 39:16)
  - 1949-1951 Photographs of Wellesley College, 3 items (Box-folder 39:17)
  - n. d. Photographs of Ann and Harry Webster and children, 40 items (Box-folder 39:18)
  - 1987-1999n. d. Photographs of Ann and Harry Webster children and grandchildren, 100 items (Box-folder 40:1)
  - n. d. Photographs of William Webster, 25 items (Box-folder 40:2)
  - n. d. Photographs of Websters (William's ancestors), 9 items (Box-folder 40:3)
  - n. d. Photographs of friends, 7 items (Box-folder 40:4)
    Includes photographs of Hoffman and Claire Wolff, Jim and Harriet Manning, and the children of James Elder.
  - n. d. Photographs of St. Anne's friends, 3 items (Box-folder 40:5)
  - n. d. negatives unidentified, 4 items (Box-folder 40:6)
  - n. d.1985 color slides, 28 items (Box-folder 40:7)
    Slides of Lindsay reunion and slides of Mexico (1985)
  - n. d. Box of daguerreotypes, 20 items (Box 40)
  - Oversize photograph, 1 item (Box 40)
    Group photograph with William Webster
  - n. d. Souvenirs miniature commercial photos, 54 items (Box-folder 40:8)
  - n. d. Souvenirs and calling cards, 49 items (Box-folder 40:9)
  - n. d. Souvenirs: cocktail napkins, 35 items (Box-folder 40:10)
  - n. d. Souvenirs Princeton, 17 items (Box-folder 40:11)
  - n. d. Souvenirs Wellesley, 29 items (Box-folder 40:12)
  - n. d. Souvenirs ink pens, # items (Box 40)
- Series V: Printed Materials
  - 1930-1968 Printed materials, 22 items (Box-folder 41:1)
    Included is a passenger list of the S. S. Independence, programs for plays, Chelsea greeting cards, and miscellaneous brochures from the Gordon and Webster family.
  - 1946-1988 Printed materials, 10 items (Box-folder 41:2)
    newsletters and pamphlets about Princeton University, Bryant College, St. James School and John Marshall College Law School.
  - 1948-1972 Printed materials, 9 items (Box-folder 41:3)
    Magazines and articles about William Webster and atomic power including a brochure on the John Fritz Medal award.
  - 1949-1971 Printed materials, 10 items (Box-folder 41:4)
    Magazines and articles about William Webster including Contact Magazine, New England Electric Company Handbook, and Utility Spotlight.